<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LinearLayout
    android:id="@+id/review"
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:layout_marginBottom="16dp"
    android:layout_marginTop="16dp"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/review_author"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:lineSpacingMultiplier="1.2"
        android:textAppearance="@style/TextAppearance.AppCompat.Body2"
        android:textColor="@android:color/white"
        tools:text="Travis Bell"/>

    <TextView
        android:id="@+id/review_content"
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:layout_marginTop="2dp"
        android:background="?android:attr/selectableItemBackground"
        android:ellipsize="end"
        android:fontFamily="sans-serif-light"
        android:lineSpacingMultiplier="1.2"
        android:maxLines="5"
        android:textAppearance="@style/TextAppearance.AppCompat.Body1"
        android:textColor="@android:color/white"
        tools:text="I felt like this was a tremendous end to Nolan's Batman trilogy. The Dark Knight Rises may very well have been the weakest of all 3 films but when you're talking about a scale of this magnitude, it still makes this one of the best movies I've seen in the past few years.\n\nI expected a little more Batman than we got (especially with a runtime of 2:45) but while the story around the fall of Bruce Wayne and Gotham City was good I didn't find it amazing. This might be in fact, one of my only criticisms—it was a long movie but still, maybe too short for the story I felt was really being told. I feel confident in saying this big of a story could have been split into two movies.\n\nThe acting, editing, pacing, soundtrack and overall theme were the same 'as-close-to-perfect' as ever with any of Christopher Nolan's other films. Man does this guy know how to make a movie!\n\nYou don't have to be a Batman fan to enjoy these movies and I hope any of you who feel this way re-consider. These 3 movies are without a doubt in my mind, the finest display of comic mythology ever told on the big screen. They are damn near perfect."/>

</LinearLayout>
